http://aatrackclub.org/terms-conditions/

Home
Youth Division
Who is AATC
Events, Workouts, Meetings
Flash News!
Events, Workouts, Meetings
Flash News!
Terms & Conditions
The AAtrackClub.org site is © 2016 Ann Arbor Track Club All rights reserved.Revised 6/01/2016IntroductionAnn Arbor Track Club ("AATC") maintains this AAtrackClub.org site for your personal information, entertainment, and enjoyment. Please feel free to browse, download from, talk back to, and otherwise use the site. At the same time, please remember that your access to the AAtrackClub.org site is subject to the following rules (the "Rules") as well as all applicable laws. By accessing and using the AAtrackClub.org site, you accept the Rules without limitation or qualification, and acknowledge that any other agreements you may have with AATC are superseded by the Rules, to the extent that conflict exists.AATC may at any time revise these Rules by updating this posting. You are bound by such revisions and should therefore visit this page to review the current Rules from time to time.AATC reserves the right, without notice and for any reason, to remove any content on this site, and to deny access of any user or users to all or any part of this site.DownloadingYou may download material displayed on the AAtrackClub.org site for personal, non-commercial use only. You must retain all copyright and other proprietary notices on downloaded and/or copied material. Any copy of material from the AAtrackClub.org site you make and distribute for any purpose must also include these Rules. You may not distribute, modify, transmit, use, or reuse any of the contents of the AAtrackClub.org site for any public or commercial purpose without the written consent of AATC or any third party AATC deems necessary.Copyrights, Other RightsYou should assume everything on the AAtrackClub.org site is copyrighted unless otherwise noted and may not be used except as provided in the Rules or with the express written consent of AATC or any third party AATC deems necessary. AATC neither warrants or represents that your use of the material displayed on the AAtrackClub.org site will not infringe rights of third parties. Any product, service, program, or technology described on the AAtrackClub.org site may be the subject of other intellectual property rights (including but not limited to copyright, trademark, or patent rights) owned by AATC. Any such right that is not expressly licensed herein is reserved by AATC.Images of people or places displayed on the AAtrackClub.org site are either the property of, or used with permission by, AATC. Use of these images by you or other third parties is prohibited unless expressly permitted in the Rules or elsewhere on the AAtrackClub.org site. Any unauthorized use of these images may violate copyright laws, trademark laws, the laws of privacy and publicity, and other applicable regulations and statutes.Any product, service, program or technology described in any document published by AATC on this site may be the subject of other intellectual property rights owned by AATC. Any such right that is not expressly licensed here under is reserved by AATC.TrademarksThe trademarks, logos, and service marks (collectively the "Trademarks") displayed on the AAtrackClub.org site are registered and unregistered Trademarks of AATC and others.  Trademark denotations on the AAtrackClub.org site indicate federal registrations in the United States.  Nothing contained on the AAtrackClub.org site should be construed as granting by implication, estoppel, or otherwise, any license or right to use any Trademark displayed on the AAtrackClub.org site without the written permission of AATC or such third party that may own the Trademark. Misuse of any Trademarks, or any other content, displayed on the AAtrackClub.org site is prohibited. AATC aggressively enforces its intellectual property rights, including via civil and criminal proceedings.SubmissionsApart from your personal information (which is addressed in the Privacy Policy), any communication or material you send to the AAtrackClub.org site, electronically or otherwise, including but not limited to data, questions, comments, suggestions, or submissions is and will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary. Anything you send to the AAtrackClub.org site may be used by AATC for any purpose including but not limited to reproduction, transmission, disclosure, publication, broadcast, and posting. By submitting material to AAtrackClub.org, you irrevocably transfer and assign to AATC, and forever waive and agree never to assert, any copyrights, "moral" rights, or other rights that you may have in such material. AATC is free to use, without obligation of any kind, any ideas, concepts, techniques, or know-how contained in any communication you send to the AAtrackClub.org site for any purpose whatsoever, including but not limited to developing, manufacturing, and marketing products and services. By using this site, you may submit, or AATC may gather, certain limited information about you and your usage of the site. Subject to the terms of the Privacy Policy, AATC is free to use such information for any purpose it deems appropriate.No WarrantiesThere is no warranty that any information or service provided or referenced by this site is either merchantable or accurate, that such information or service will fulfill any of your particular purposes or needs, or that such information or service does not infringe on any third party rights. Except for any express warranties stated on this site, if any, the information and services provided or referenced on this site are provided "as is" and with all faults, and the entire risk as to satisfactory quality, performance, accuracy and effort is with the user.So, while AATC uses reasonable efforts to include accurate and up-to-date information on the AAtrackClub.org site, AATC makes no warranties or representations as to its accuracy.  AATC may periodically add, change, or improve any of the information, products, services, programs, and technology described on the AAtrackClub.org site without notice. AATC assumes no liability or responsibility for any errors or omissions in the content of the AAtrackClub.org site.In fact, your use of the AAtrackClub.org site is at your own risk. Neither AATC nor any other party involved in creating, producing, or delivering the AAtrackClub.org site is liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, consequential, or punitive damages arising out of your access to, or use of, the AAtrackClub.org site. For example, AATC assumes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for any damages to or any viruses which may affect your computer equipment or other property on account of your access to, use of, or downloading from, the AAtrackClub.org site. Please note that some jurisdictions may not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, so some of the above exclusions may not apply to you.LinksAATC has not reviewed all of the sites which are linked to the AAtrackClub.org site, and the fact of such links does not indicate any approval or endorsement of any material contained on any linked site.  AATC is not responsible for the contents of any site linked to the AAtrackClub.org site; your connection to any such linked site is at your own risk.U.S., International InformationMost of the information on the AAtrackClub.org site applies internationally, but a significant amount of information applies only to certain countries or regions. For instance, if you see the following indication in connection with information on the AAtrackClub.org site:The information on this page applies to businesses in the U.S.then that information applies only to businesses operating in the U.S. If you live outside of the U.S., the fact that you have access to such U.S.-specific information does not mean that such information applies or ever will apply to your country or region. Although AATC tries to mark all country- and region-specific information with this form of indication, it does not warrant or represent that all information without this indication applies internationally. You should check the applicability of any information on this site to you or your organization.Really Legal StuffThe Rules will be governed by and construed under the laws of the State of Michigan. Each party to the AAtrackClub.org site Rules hereby submits to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts within the State of Michigan, and waives any jurisdictional venue or inconvenient forum objections to such courts. Any failure by AATC to enforce any of its rights under the Rules or applicable laws shall not constitute a waiver of such right. If any provision of the Rules is found by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, you, AATC, and the court shall endeavor to give effect to the intent reflected in that provision, and the remaining Rules provisions shall retain their full force and effect.United States and foreign export control laws regulate the export and re-export of technology originating in the United States and such foreign countries. You will abide by these laws and regulations as applicable and will not transfer, directly or indirectly, by electronic transmission or otherwise, any content or software from the AAtrackClub.org site to or from any countries or foreign nationals in violation of such laws or regulations. Please also read over the AAtrackClub.org site Privacy Policy. If you have any questions, comments, criticisms, or complaints about AAtrackClub.org, please feel free to email us.
Our SponsorsMore About AATC News & Media
Calendar
Follow Us!
This is a staging environment for testing purposes — no orders shall be fulfilled.
